<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>spacecraft - object - satdh</title>
        <link>/objects/spacecraft/</link>
        <description>spacecraft - object - satdh</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 12:13:31 &#43;0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/objects/spacecraft/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Starlink Constellation</title>
    <link>/articles/starlink-constellation/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 12:13:31 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>/articles/starlink-constellation/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Starlink is a satellite internet constellation being constructed by SpaceX. It is designed to provide low-cost, high-speed internet access to people in remote and rural areas around the world. The constellation consists of thousands of small satellites in low Earth orbit, which communicate with each other and with ground stations to provide internet access.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Satellite Remote Sensing: Strategic, Technological, and Economic Aspects</title>
    <link>/articles/satellite-remote-sensing-strategic-technological-and-economic-aspects/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 12:13:31 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>/articles/satellite-remote-sensing-strategic-technological-and-economic-aspects/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Remote sensing refers to the process of acquiring information about an object or phenomenon from a distance. This information is collected using instruments or sensors that are mounted on platforms such as satellites, aircraft, or drones. The technology has revolutionized the way we study and understand our planet, as well as opened up new opportunities for research and application in a wide range of fields.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>SpaceX’s Polaris Dawn: The Most Ambitious Private Space Mission Ever</title>
    <link>/articles/spacexs-polaris-dawn-the-most-ambitious-private-space-mission-ever/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 12:13:31 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>/articles/spacexs-polaris-dawn-the-most-ambitious-private-space-mission-ever/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Polaris Dawn is a historic private space mission that will try to reach the highest Earth orbit ever flown by humans. The mission is part of the Polaris Program, a visionary initiative that aims to inspire humanity and advance space exploration through three groundbreaking missions: Polaris Dawn, Polaris Starlight and Polaris Moonlight.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
