<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>public sector - actor - satdh</title>
        <link>/actors/public-sector/</link>
        <description>public sector - actor - satdh</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 12:13:31 &#43;0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/actors/public-sector/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Moon Race: Exploring Challenges and Opportunities</title>
    <link>/articles/moon-race-challenges-opportunities/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 12:13:31 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>/articles/moon-race-challenges-opportunities/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[In this article, we&rsquo;ll delve into the strategic, geopolitical and technological aspects of moon exploration and exploitation, exploring the potential benefits and challenges involved. We&rsquo;ll examine initiatives by leading countries such as US (NASA, Elon Musk), China, Russia and Europe and discuss the role of moon exploration and exploitation in geopolitical strategy.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Balancing Competition: The Importance of Space Diplomacy</title>
    <link>/articles/balancing-competition-space-diplomacy/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 12:13:31 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>/articles/balancing-competition-space-diplomacy/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Space diplomacy is the diplomatic effort to balance competition, promote cooperation and protect interests in the exploration and use of outer space. International treaties, initiatives and an understanding of the unique needs and priorities of different interests in the space sector are crucial to ensuring stability and a peaceful future.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>The Geopolitical Chessboard in Space: Navigating the Implications</title>
    <link>/articles/geopolitical-chessboard-space-implications/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 12:13:31 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>/articles/geopolitical-chessboard-space-implications/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[This article analyses the political and geopolitical effects of space exploration using Astropolitik and other sources. It discusses the need for a consistent legal and political framework for space activities, balancing commercial and national interests with sustainability and safety, and the risks of great power competition in space. The post promotes space exploration cooperation and the Thucydides Trap.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
