<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>usa - country - satdh</title>
        <link>/countries/usa/</link>
        <description>usa - country - satdh</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 12:13:31 &#43;0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/countries/usa/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>The Moon: Challenges and Opportunities</title>
    <link>/articles/the-moon-challenges-and-opportunities/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 12:13:31 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>/articles/the-moon-challenges-and-opportunities/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[In this article, we&rsquo;ll delve into the strategic, geopolitical, and technological aspects of moon exploration and exploitation, exploring the potential benefits and challenges involved. We&rsquo;ll examine initiatives by leading countries such as US (NASA, Elon Musk), China, Russia, and Europe, and discuss the role of moon exploration and exploitation in geopolitical strategy.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Satellite Remote Sensing: Strategic, Technological, and Economic Aspects</title>
    <link>/articles/satellite-remote-sensing-strategic-technological-and-economic-aspects/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 12:13:31 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>/articles/satellite-remote-sensing-strategic-technological-and-economic-aspects/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Remote sensing refers to the process of acquiring information about an object or phenomenon from a distance. This information is collected using instruments or sensors that are mounted on platforms such as satellites, aircraft, or drones. The technology has revolutionized the way we study and understand our planet, as well as opened up new opportunities for research and application in a wide range of fields.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Space Diplomacy</title>
    <link>/articles/space-diplomacy/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 12:13:31 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>/articles/space-diplomacy/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Space diplomacy is the diplomatic effort to balance competition, promote cooperation, and protect interests in the exploration and use of outer space. International treaties, initiatives, and an understanding of the unique needs and priorities of different interests in the space sector are crucial to ensuring stability and a peaceful future.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>SpaceX’s Polaris Dawn: The Most Ambitious Private Space Mission Ever</title>
    <link>/articles/spacexs-polaris-dawn-the-most-ambitious-private-space-mission-ever/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 12:13:31 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>/articles/spacexs-polaris-dawn-the-most-ambitious-private-space-mission-ever/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Polaris Dawn is a historic private space mission that will try to reach the highest Earth orbit ever flown by humans. The mission is part of the Polaris Program, a visionary initiative that aims to inspire humanity and advance space exploration through three groundbreaking missions: Polaris Dawn, Polaris Starlight and Polaris Moonlight.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
