<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on satdh</title>
    <link>/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on satdh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><atom:link href="/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>The SATDH site. Welcome to the satdh.com blog on space strategy, systems, and technologies! We are a group of space enthusiasts and experts who are interested in learning about the most recent advancements in this field. Our blog is dedicated to providing valuable insights, updates, and information about space strategy, systems, and technologies. You&amp;rsquo;ll find a wide range of topics covered here, from the most recent space missions and innovations to in-depth analyses of current and future space industry trends. We aim to make our content accessible to readers with varying levels of knowledge and expertise, whether you&amp;rsquo;re a student, a professional, or just someone curious about space.
Tagging System When it comes to finding the information you need, we understand the importance of organization and accessibility. That is why we have implemented a comprehensive tagging system to help you find what you are looking for. Each post is tagged with relevant keywords, making it easy to find and search for posts on specific topics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/pages/tagging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pages/tagging/</guid>
      <description>Taxonomies Putting things or ideas into different groups is a good way to keep information organized and make it easier to find. Taxonomies, which are sets of categories organized in a hierarchy, are often used to help with this. A good taxonomy can make it easier for people to find the information they need and help make sure things are put in the right category. An important part of a taxonomy&amp;rsquo;s effectiveness is how easy it is for users to move around and find information. There is no one way to put things into groups. The best way to do this is to adapt to the situation. Items on this site are sorted into four different groups by the labels shown below.
The Objects click here to expand Spacecraft A spacecraft is a vehicle or machine designed to function in space. It can include a wide range of objects, such as satellites, probes, rovers, landers, and human-rated vehicles like the International Space Station (ISS) and the Space Shuttle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/pages/tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pages/tool/</guid>
      <description>webtools file</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
