<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on satdh</title>
    <link>/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on satdh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><atom:link href="/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>about us</title>
      <link>/pages/aboutus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pages/aboutus/</guid>
      <description>Purposes Share the core values and vision that drive your website. Discuss the principles, beliefs, or philosophies that guide your work. This allows visitors to understand the underlying motivations and perspectives that shape your content or offerings. FAQ A FAQ page, short for Frequently Asked Questions, is a space where important information about a business is shared to clarify questions and uncertainties on the part of shoppers. FAQ pages serve a utilitarian purpose first and foremost, grouping information about the site, shipping and other concerns together in a single, searchable document.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>classes (taxonomy)</title>
      <link>/pages/classes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pages/classes/</guid>
      <description>‎The Four Causes of ‎Space Exploration‎objects‎spacecrafts‎launchers‎stations‎actors‎business‎public sector‎science‎purposes‎exploitation‎research‎services‎fields‎strategies‎programs‎tecnologies Introduction The proposed &amp;ldquo;Four Causes of Space Exploration&amp;rdquo; classification system organizes space-related topics into four main classes: Objects, Actors, Purposes and Fields.
Objects: Refers to spacecraft, launchers (devices to propel objects into space), and stations (facilities for habitation or spacecraft control). Actors: Involves businesses in the private sector, the public sector (government agencies and regulatory bodies), and the scientific community. Purposes: Includes commercial use of outer space, research to enhance our understanding of the universe, and space-based services to Earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>filter</title>
      <link>/pages/filter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pages/filter/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
